[
    {
        "question": "An outcast prince takes over the revolution by controlling the mind of others. Who is he?",
        "answers": [
            "Lelouch Lanperouge",
            "Ling Yao",
            "Prince Vegeta",
            "Canute",
            "Meliodas",
            "Bruno von Grannzreich",
            "Sinbad"
        ],
        "answer": "Lelouch Lanperouge"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sells his soul to a demon in search of protection and revenge against his parents\u00e2\u20ac\u2122 death?",
        "answers": [
            "Ciel Phantomhive",
            "Cuphead",
            "Mugman",
            "Naofumi",
            "Madoka Magica",
            "Hell Girl",
            "Jigoku Shoujo"
        ],
        "answer": "Ciel Phantomhive"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which members of \u2018Suzaku 7\u2019 in \u2018Fushigi Yugi\u2019 are never killed?",
        "answers": [
            "Miaka and Keisuke",
            "Hotohori and Suzaku",
            "Nuriko and Yui",
            "Yui and Keisuke",
            "Tusuki and Chichiri"
        ],
        "answer": "Tusuki and Chichiri"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which boy became the youngest State Alchemist at the age of twelve?",
        "answers": [
            "Alphonse Elric",
            "Scar",
            "Roy Mustang",
            "Riza Hawkeye",
            "Van Hohenheim",
            "Edward Elric"
        ],
        "answer": "Edward Elric"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vegeta married a sharp-minded scientist. Who was she?",
        "answers": [
            "Yamcha",
            "Chi Chi",
            "Krillin",
            "Mirai",
            "Bulma"
        ],
        "answer": "Bulma"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lover of sweets and mysteries, which genius is a world-famous detective?",
        "answers": [
            "James Moriarty",
            "Vanitas",
            "Sherlock Holmes",
            "Ranpo Edogawa",
            "Norman (Promised Neverland)",
            "L Lawliet"
        ],
        "answer": "L Lawliet"
    },
    {
        "question": "As prophesized, Goku transformed into the Super Saiyan form in \u2018Dragon Ball Z\u2019. Where did this transformation take place?",
        "answers": [
            "Earth",
            "Planet Vegeta",
            "Planet Freiza",
            "Universe 7",
            "Mars",
            "Saturn",
            "Planet Namek"
        ],
        "answer": "Planet Namek"
    },
    {
        "question": "This pink-haired girl is completely obsessed with her love for Yuki, which she professes in her \u2018Yukiteru diary\u2019. Who is she?",
        "answers": [
            "Yuno Grinberryall",
            "Asta",
            "Ichika",
            "Natsu",
            "Zero Two",
            "Yuri Nakamura",
            "Ringo Haruno",
            "Hisoka",
            "Yuno Gasai"
        ],
        "answer": "Yuno Gasai"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the shinigami in love with apples?",
        "answers": [
            "Armonia",
            "Calikarcha",
            "Daril",
            "Gelus",
            "Nu",
            "Midora",
            "Rem",
            "Ridoh",
            "Ryuk"
        ],
        "answer": "Ryuk"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is known as the \u2018One Punch Man\u2019?",
        "answers": [
            "Genos",
            "Bill Gates",
            "Goku",
            "Joeseph Joestar",
            "Deku",
            "Saitama"
        ],
        "answer": "Saitama"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you know who voiced our metallic Alchemist, Alphonse Elric from \u2018Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood\u2019?",
        "answers": [
            "Rie Takahasi",
            "Veronica Taylor",
            "Satoshi Tajiri",
            "Akari Kitou",
            "Touyama Nao",
            "Rie Kugimiya"
        ],
        "answer": "Rie Kugimiya"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the voice actor behind the catching pika-pika of Pikachu from \u2018Pokemon\u2019.",
        "answers": [
            "Miyuki Sawashiro",
            "Yui Ishikawa",
            "Marina Inoue",
            "Romi Park",
            "Ayane Sakura",
            "Yuu Shimamura",
            "Ikue Otani"
        ],
        "answer": "Ikue Otani"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the creator of the heart-touching movie \u2018Spirited Away\u2019 (2001)?",
        "answers": [
            "Koyoharu Gotouge",
            "Gege Akutami",
            "Afro",
            "ONE",
            "Hayao Miyazaki"
        ],
        "answer": "Hayao Miyazaki"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayato Date is the director of which mega-hit anime series?",
        "answers": [
            "One Piece",
            "Bleach",
            "Dragon BallZ",
            "Fairy Tail",
            "Boruto",
            "Black Clover",
            "Naruto"
        ],
        "answer": "Naruto"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote and illustrated the manga on which \u2018One Piece\u2019 is based?",
        "answers": [
            "Masashi Kishimoto",
            "Chiaki Inabi",
            "Akira Toriyama",
            "Yoshi Togashi",
            "Naoko Takeuchi",
            "Eiichiro Oda"
        ],
        "answer": "Eiichiro Oda"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many characters do Goku kill in the \u2018Dragon Ball Z\u2019 series?",
        "answers": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "",
            "",
            "14",
            "2"
        ],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the greatest taboo for the alchemists in \u2018Fullmetal Alchemist\u2019?",
        "answers": [
            "The Truth",
            "Homunculus",
            "Philosopher's Stone",
            "7 sins",
            "Human transmutation"
        ],
        "answer": "Human transmutation"
    },
    {
        "question": "The corgi named Einstein appears in this anime.",
        "answers": [
            "Cells at Work!",
            "Creating Electricity",
            "Code Geass",
            "Love Lab",
            "Hunter x Hunter",
            "Cowboy Bepop"
        ],
        "answer": "Cowboy Bepop"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first character in \u2018Dragon Ball Z\u2019 who achieved the Super Saiyan 2?",
        "answers": [
            "Future Trunks",
            "Kid Trunks",
            "Goten",
            "Goku",
            "Vegeta",
            "Broly",
            "Gohan"
        ],
        "answer": "Gohan"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime \u2018Hunter X Hunter\u2019, which family is famous for being assassins?",
        "answers": [
            "Gon's Family",
            "Kurapika's Family",
            "Hisoka's Family",
            "Leorio's Family",
            "Killua's Family"
        ],
        "answer": "Killua's Family"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which thing is used to restore a Z fighter to his full health after being severely wounded?",
        "answers": [
            "Shenron",
            "Senzu Candy",
            "Sacred Water",
            "Ensenji",
            "Medical Machine",
            "Senzu Bean"
        ],
        "answer": "Senzu Bean"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ciel Phantomhive has been engaged to marry which character?",
        "answers": [
            "Angelina Dalles",
            "Mey-rin",
            "Hannah Annafellows",
            "Queen Victoria",
            "Francis Midford",
            "Ran-Mao",
            "Elizabeth Midford"
        ],
        "answer": "Elizabeth Midford"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first member of the First Levi Squad to die in \u2018Attack on Titan\u2019?",
        "answers": [
            "Eid Jinn",
            "Oluo Bozado",
            "Petra Ral",
            "Sasha Blouse",
            "Gunther"
        ],
        "answer": "Gunther"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the supernatural ability that Lelouch gains from C.C. that lets him control others?",
        "answers": [
            "Brainwashing",
            "Je t'aime",
            "Zanpakuto",
            "Mind Stitching",
            "Geass"
        ],
        "answer": "Geass"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \u2018One Piece\u2019, one of the priests in the Skypiea era is Ohm. What is his dog\u2019s name?",
        "answers": [
            "Fields",
            "Einstein",
            "Lightning",
            "Max",
            "Za Warudo",
            "Styles",
            "Law",
            "Holy"
        ],
        "answer": "Holy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the zombie, Ryuuma, in \u2018One Piece\u2019, who possessed Brooke\u2019s shadow in the Thriller Bark Arc?",
        "answers": [
            "Swordsman",
            "Gunman",
            "Devil Fruit User",
            "Haki User",
            "Martial Artist",
            "Samurai"
        ],
        "answer": "Samurai"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose Zanpakuto is Wabisuke in \u2018Bleach\u2019 and had a crush on Hinamori Momo?",
        "answers": [
            "Ichigo Kurosaki",
            "Yoruichi Shihounin",
            "Rangiku Matsumoto",
            "Rukia Kuchiki",
            "Sosuke Aizen",
            "Kira Izuru"
        ],
        "answer": "Kira Izuru"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ghouls cannot eat human food as it tastes bad to them and makes them sick. There is an exception to this. Which human food they can consume without any reactions?",
        "answers": [
            "Apple",
            "Cake",
            "Water",
            "Beef",
            "Pork",
            "Coffee"
        ],
        "answer": "Coffee"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kaneki was tortured for ten days. Even his hair turned white from black, and his fingers and toes were cut off. Who did this to him?",
        "answers": [
            "Yamaguchi",
            "Yamamoto",
            "Yamcha",
            "Yamori"
        ],
        "answer": "Yamori"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \u2018Clannad\u2019, when Sanae first met Okazaki, which kind of bread does she offer to him?",
        "answers": [
            "Baguette",
            "Paan",
            "Salty Pretzel Bread",
            "Sweet Cloud Bread",
            "Sweet Bean Bread"
        ],
        "answer": "Sweet Bean Bread"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is actually manga?",
        "answers": [
            "A form of video game",
            "A form of comics",
            "A form of animation"
        ],
        "answer": "A form of animation"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the first season of In Sword Art Online, what is the black blade used by Kirito called?",
        "answers": [
            "Blue Dragon",
            "Rising Sun",
            "Black Dragon",
            "Darkness",
            "The Elucidator"
        ],
        "answer": "The Elucidator"
    },
    {
        "question": "As of 2021, what is the highest-grossing anime movies of all time?",
        "answers": [
            "Your Name",
            "Howl\u2019s Moving Castle",
            "Silent Voice",
            "Spirited Away",
            "Demon Slayer: Mugen Train"
        ],
        "answer": "Demon Slayer: Mugen Train"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the main character of the anime Pok\u00e9mon?",
        "answers": [
            "Misty",
            "Professor Samuel Oak",
            "Professor Oak",
            "Dawn",
            "Misty",
            "Brock",
            "Ash Ketchum"
        ],
        "answer": "Ash Ketchum"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Dragon Ball, what can you do after collecting all seven dragon balls?",
        "answers": [
            "To become immortal",
            "To rule the world",
            "To fulfil your wishes"
        ],
        "answer": "To fulfil your wishes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Attack on Titan, the main characters were trained in the army to fight against Titans. What are actually Titans?",
        "answers": [
            "Giant monsters",
            "Dinosaurs",
            "Unknown",
            "Mutant Animals",
            "Ex-Humans"
        ],
        "answer": "Ex-Humans"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following anime features a character called Sophie?",
        "answers": [
            "Go! Princess PreCure",
            "Sailor Moon",
            "Howl\u2019s Moving Castle"
        ],
        "answer": "Howl\u2019s Moving Castle"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is special about the giant cat in the anime My Neighbour Totoro?",
        "answers": [
            "It is also a plane",
            "It is also a ship",
            "It is also a bus"
        ],
        "answer": "It is also a bus"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Fairy Tail, which kind of wizard is Lucy?",
        "answers": [
            "Fire Dragon Slayer Wizard",
            "Ice-Make Wizard",
            "God Slayer Wizard",
            "Crash Magic Wizard",
            "Celestial Wizard"
        ],
        "answer": "Celestial Wizard"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Gum-Gum Pistol is a signature attack of which anime character?",
        "answers": [
            "Black Butler",
            "Chobits",
            "Chopper",
            "Gojou Satorou",
            "Saitama",
            "Genos",
            "Monkey D. Luffy"
        ],
        "answer": "Monkey D. Luffy"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Fullmetal Alchemist, which Homunculi is created when Alphonse and Edward Elric used alchemy to bring their mom back to life?",
        "answers": [
            "Greed",
            "Envy",
            "Wrath",
            "Lust",
            "Sloth"
        ],
        "answer": "Sloth"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Death Note, who was the first successor of L in the Kira investigation?",
        "answers": [
            "Mikami",
            "Mello",
            "Near",
            "Misa",
            "Light Yagami"
        ],
        "answer": "Light Yagami"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Hunter X Hunter, who is the father of Gon Freecss?",
        "answers": [
            "Mito Freecss",
            "Ging Freecss",
            "Jinx Freecss",
            "Hisoka Freecss",
            "Kite Freecss"
        ],
        "answer": "Ging Freecss"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Japanese anime studio is known for famous works, such as Princess Mononoke, Grave of the Fireflies, Spirited Away, and My Neighbour Totoro?",
        "answers": [
            "Kyoto Animation,Studio Bones",
            "Ufotable",
            "Mappa",
            "Wit Studio",
            "Funimation",
            "Studio Ghibli"
        ],
        "answer": "Studio Ghibli"
    },
    {
        "question": "Haikyu!! is an anime centred around a boy who wants to be successful in which sport?",
        "answers": [
            "Basketball",
            "Baseball",
            "Swimming",
            "Golfing",
            "Bowling",
            "Volleyball"
        ],
        "answer": "Volleyball"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following facts is NOT true about Doraemon in the anime of the same name?",
        "answers": [
            "Doraemon is a robotic cat",
            "Doraemon has no ears",
            "Doraemon has one brother and one sister"
        ],
        "answer": "Doraemon has one brother and one sister"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Fairy Tail, Natsu is able to absorb and reflect nearly all types of attack from which two elements?",
        "answers": [
            "Water and Wind",
            "Ice and Fire",
            "Shadow and Fire",
            "Light and Fire",
            "Lightning and Fire"
        ],
        "answer": "Lightning and Fire"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the meaning of Deku, the nickname of Izuku Midoriya in the anime My Hero Academia?",
        "answers": [
            "A nerd who loves playing game",
            "A good friend",
            "useful",
            "a NEET",
            "A person who cannot do anything"
        ],
        "answer": "A person who cannot do anything"
    },
    {
        "question": "Goku belongs to which race in the anime Dragon Ball?",
        "answers": [
            "Namekian",
            "Majin",
            "Human",
            "Saiyan"
        ],
        "answer": "Saiyan"
    },
    {
        "question": "In season 1 of the anime Bleach, who is the Lieutenant of the 11th Division?",
        "answers": [
            "Yachiru Kusajishi",
            "Yumichika Ayasegawa",
            "Ichigo",
            "Ikkaku Madarame"
        ],
        "answer": "Ikkaku Madarame"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime Code Geass, the character C.C. is known for her obsession with which food?",
        "answers": [
            "French Fries",
            "Hamburgers",
            "Sushi",
            "Spaghetti",
            "Pizza"
        ],
        "answer": "Pizza"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the strongest meister who has ever graduated from Death Weapon Meister Academy in the anime Soul Eater?",
        "answers": [
            "Ox Ford",
            "Death the Kid",
            "Franken Stein"
        ],
        "answer": "Franken Stein"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the older brother of Inuyasha in the anime of the same name?",
        "answers": [
            "Toga",
            "Naraku",
            "Naruto",
            "Souma",
            "Nagisa",
            "Sesshomaru"
        ],
        "answer": "Sesshomaru"
    },
    {
        "question": "What surrounds the area where humans live?",
        "answers": [
            "Titans",
            "Police",
            "Marley",
            "Walls"
        ],
        "answer": "Walls"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the innermost wall?",
        "answers": [
            "Wall Rose",
            "Wall Maria",
            "Wall Sheena"
        ],
        "answer": "Wall Sheena"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the second outermost wall?",
        "answers": [
            "Wall Maria",
            "Wall Sheena",
            "Wall Rose"
        ],
        "answer": "Wall Rose"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the outermost wall protecting the humans called?",
        "answers": [
            "Wall Rose",
            "Wall Sheena",
            "Wall Maria"
        ],
        "answer": "Wall Maria"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which branch of the military protects the Royal Family?",
        "answers": [
            "Cadet Corps",
            "Scout Regiment",
            "Garrison Regiment",
            "Titan",
            "Military Police Brigade"
        ],
        "answer": "Military Police Brigade"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Eren\u2019s adopted sister?",
        "answers": [
            "Ymir",
            "Historia",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa Ackerman"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa Ackerman"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which family member does Eren watch get eaten by a Titan?",
        "answers": [
            "Sister",
            "Father",
            "Best Friend",
            "Brother",
            "Mother"
        ],
        "answer": "Mother"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the story, who is the first human shown to be a Titan?",
        "answers": [
            "Reiner",
            "Bertholtd",
            "Annie",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Eren\u2019s best friend?",
        "answers": [
            "Mikasa",
            "Historia",
            "Jean",
            "Connie",
            "Reiner",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which branch of the military tries to reclaim land from Titans?",
        "answers": [
            "Cadet Corps",
            "Garrison Regiment",
            "Military Police Regiment",
            "Scout Regiment"
        ],
        "answer": "Scout Regiment"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is considered \u201chumanity\u2019s strongest soldier?\u201d",
        "answers": [
            "Saitama",
            "All Might",
            "Endeavor",
            "Tanya Degurechaff",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Levi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Female Titan (AOT)?",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Reiner",
            "Bertholtd",
            "Historia",
            "Gabi",
            "Annie"
        ],
        "answer": "Annie"
    },
    {
        "question": "What number is Eren\u2019s training squad in Attack on Titan?",
        "answers": [
            "101st",
            "103rd",
            "112th",
            "96th",
            "104th"
        ],
        "answer": "104th"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest a Titan can be?",
        "answers": [
            "1 meter",
            "5 meters",
            "7 meters",
            "1.5 meters",
            "3 meters"
        ],
        "answer": "3 meters"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was developed especially to fight the Armored Titan?",
        "answers": [
            "ODM Gear",
            "3D Manuever Gear",
            "Nichirin Blades",
            "Thunder Spears"
        ],
        "answer": "Thunder Spears"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is in charge of the defense of the southern region?",
        "answers": [
            "Erwin Smith",
            "Levi Ackerman",
            "Zoe Hange",
            "Dot Pixis"
        ],
        "answer": "Dot Pixis"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nickname was given to Erwin when he was a child?",
        "answers": [
            "Smith",
            "Eric",
            "Pee Pee",
            "Cold Eye",
            "Eyebrows"
        ],
        "answer": "Eyebrows"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the race that can turn into Titans?",
        "answers": [
            "Marleyan",
            "Eldians",
            "Devils of the Island",
            "Paradis",
            "Subjects of Ymir"
        ],
        "answer": "Subjects of Ymir"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mike was the second strongest soldier in the Scouting Legion.",
        "answers": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What\u2019s Naruto\u2019s mom\u2019s name?",
        "answers": [
            "Hinata",
            "Sakura",
            "Uchiha",
            "Konohagurake",
            "Kushina"
        ],
        "answer": "Kushina"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the village where Naruto lives called?",
        "answers": [
            "Kumogakure",
            "Otogakure",
            "Sunagakure",
            "Takigakure",
            "Konohagurake"
        ],
        "answer": "Konohagurake"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Tsunade\u2019s \u201cdrug\u201d (Naruto)?",
        "answers": [
            "Eating",
            "Senzu Bean",
            "Young Men",
            "Naruto",
            "Gambling"
        ],
        "answer": "Gambling"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Naruto eventually marry?",
        "answers": [
            "Sakura",
            "Sasuke",
            "Itachi",
            "Tsunade",
            "Haku",
            "Hinata"
        ],
        "answer": "Hinata"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the youngest Jonin (Naruto)?",
        "answers": [
            "Sasuke",
            "Naruto",
            "Sakura",
            "Kakashi"
        ],
        "answer": "Kakashi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Madara\u2019s Jutsu?",
        "answers": [
            "Rasengan",
            "Chakra",
            "Blood Moon Eyes",
            "Moonlight Eyes",
            "Eye of the Moon"
        ],
        "answer": "Eye of the Moon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Jutsu is Naruto most proficient in?",
        "answers": [
            "Sexy Jutsu",
            "Rasengan",
            "Nine Tail Fox",
            "Shadow Clone Jutsu"
        ],
        "answer": "Shadow Clone Jutsu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What must you know about a person to use the Death Note?",
        "answers": [
            "Name",
            "Face",
            "Last Name",
            "Life Span",
            "Name and Face"
        ],
        "answer": "Name and Face"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do Shinigami eyes allow you to see?",
        "answers": [
            "lifespan",
            "person's name",
            "person's face",
            "A person\u2019s name and lifespan"
        ],
        "answer": "A person\u2019s name and lifespan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the default method of death inflicted by the Death Note?",
        "answers": [
            "Suicide",
            "Car Accident",
            "Lung Failure",
            "Heart Attack"
        ],
        "answer": "Heart Attack"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only thing that can kill a shinigami?",
        "answers": [
            "Writing it's name in the death note",
            "Find the shinigami's true name",
            "Saving a human\u2019s life"
        ],
        "answer": "Saving a human\u2019s life"
    },
    {
        "question": "As the series comes to an end, who kills L?",
        "answers": [
            "Rem",
            "Ryuk",
            "Light",
            "Near",
            "Mello",
            "Misa"
        ],
        "answer": "Rem"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the end, who kills Light?",
        "answers": [
            "Rem",
            "Near",
            "Mello",
            "One of the FBI Agents",
            "Ryuk"
        ],
        "answer": "Ryuk"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which anime series is Ash Ketchum the main character?",
        "answers": [
            "Eyeshield 21",
            "Cowboy Bebop",
            "Super Dimension Fortress",
            "Macross",
            "Pokemon"
        ],
        "answer": "Pokemon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dragon Ball\u2019 was created by who in 1984?",
        "answers": [
            "Satoshi Tajiri",
            "Hirohiko Araki",
            "Hayao Miyazaki",
            "Akira Toriyama"
        ],
        "answer": "Akira Toriyama"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Studio Ghibli\u2019s well-known mascot?",
        "answers": [
            "Ponyo",
            "Bakura",
            "Kiki",
            "Totoro"
        ],
        "answer": "Totoro"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \u2018Sailor Moon\u2019 the anime character Makoto Kino transforms",
        "answers": [
            "Sailor Venus",
            "Sailor Mercury",
            "Sailor Mars",
            "Sailor Jupiter"
        ],
        "answer": "Sailor Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \u2018Naruto\u2019, the main character, Naruto Uzumaki, is a host for the powerful Nine-Tales. What creature is the Nine-Tails?",
        "answers": [
            "Wolf",
            "Bear",
            "Cat",
            "Fox"
        ],
        "answer": "Fox"
    },
    {
        "question": "Yubaba is a witch in which animated film written and directed by Hayao Miyazaki?",
        "answers": [
            "Castle in the Sky",
            "Ocean Waves",
            "Pom Poko",
            "Spirited Away"
        ],
        "answer": "Spirited Away"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which anime series is set in the world of Amestris?",
        "answers": [
            "Naruto",
            "Sailor Moon",
            "Pokemon",
            "Fullmetal Alchemist"
        ],
        "answer": "Fullmetal Alchemist"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \u2018Howl\u2019s Moving Castle\u2019, Sophie is transformed into an old woman by a witch. How old is Sophie as an old woman?",
        "answers": [
            "75 years old",
            "87 years old",
            "101 years old",
            "90 years old"
        ],
        "answer": "90 years old"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \u2018One Piece\u2019, Monkey D. Luffy originally sets out with the Straw Hat Pirates to become the pirate king on which ship?",
        "answers": [
            "Jolly Roger",
            "Thousand Sunny",
            "Ever Darker",
            "Going Merry"
        ],
        "answer": "Going Merry"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which anime series are Chief Daisuke Aramaki and Major Motoko Kusanag two of the main characters?",
        "answers": [
            "Cowboy Bebop",
            "Fullmetal Alchemist",
            "Paranoia Agent",
            "Id:Invaded",
            "Dominion",
            "Ghost in the Shell"
        ],
        "answer": "Ghost in the Shell"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sport is the focus of \u2018Eyeshield 21\u2019?",
        "answers": [
            "Baseball",
            "Volleyball",
            "Soccer",
            "Tennis",
            "Basketball",
            "Football"
        ],
        "answer": "Football"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following series is about time travel?",
        "answers": [
            "Darker than Black",
            "City Hunter",
            "Devilman",
            "Steins;Gate"
        ],
        "answer": "Steins;Gate"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Pok\u00e9mon is the mascot of the franchise?",
        "answers": [
            "Jigglypuff",
            "Ash Ketchum",
            "Bulbasaur",
            "Charmander",
            "Squirtle",
            "Pikachu"
        ],
        "answer": "Pikachu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Deku\u2019s Quirk in My Hero Academia?",
        "answers": [
            "One for All",
            "Half Hot Half Cold",
            "Explosion",
            "Extreme Strength",
            "One Punch",
            "All for One"
        ],
        "answer": "One for All"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Saitama\u2019s superhero name in the association?",
        "answers": [
            "One Punch Man",
            "A Hero for Fun",
            "Bald Man",
            "Caped Baldy"
        ],
        "answer": "Caped Baldy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sailor Neptune and Uranus\u2019 love story was censored in the USA dub",
        "answers": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Full Metal Alchemist, what is the principle that limits alchemy?",
        "answers": [
            "Human Transmutation",
            "The Gate of Truth",
            "Philosopher's Stone",
            "Equivalent Exchange"
        ],
        "answer": "Equivalent Exchange"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Mob\u2019s alternative form in Mob Psycho 100?",
        "answers": [
            "Psycho Mode",
            "50% Mode",
            "Half Human Half Demon",
            "100% Mode"
        ],
        "answer": "100% Mode"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Japanese film studio began in 1985?",
        "answers": [
            "Kyoto Animation",
            "Mappa",
            "Wit Studio",
            "Studio Ghibli"
        ],
        "answer": "Studio Ghibli"
    },
    {
        "question": "What famous genre is known as \u2018Boy\u2019s Love\u2019?",
        "answers": [
            "Yuri",
            "Ecchi",
            "Isekai",
            "Yaoi"
        ],
        "answer": "Yaoi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does OVA means?",
        "answers": [
            "Off Video Adaptation",
            "One-off Video Adaptation",
            "Original Video Animations"
        ],
        "answer": "Original Video Animations"
    },
    {
        "question": "Demon Slayer: Infinity Train became the highest-grossing anime and Japanese film of all time \u2013 True or False?",
        "answers": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Dragon Ball Z, how far back in time does future Trunks travel?",
        "answers": [
            "10 years",
            "100 years",
            "200 years",
            "20 years"
        ],
        "answer": "20 years"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does \u2018Baka\u2019 mean?",
        "answers": [
            "Pedophile",
            "Gay",
            "Pervert",
            "Fool"
        ],
        "answer": "Fool"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the main protagonist of Food Wars?",
        "answers": [
            "Erina Nakiri",
            "Ikumi Mito",
            "Ryoko Sakaki",
            "Alice Nakiri",
            "Soma Yukihara"
        ],
        "answer": "Soma Yukihara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Studio Ghibli film won an Academy Award in 2003?",
        "answers": [
            "Howl's Moving Castle",
            "Your Name",
            "A Silent Voice",
            "Spirited Away"
        ],
        "answer": "Spirited Away"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Sailor Moon, Tuxedo Mask and Sailor Moon are reincarnated lovers \u2013 True or False?",
        "answers": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "The anime The Seven Deadly Sins have been inspired by religions \u2013 True or False?",
        "answers": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Might Guy\u2019s rival in Naruto?",
        "answers": [
            "Rock Lee",
            "Naruto Uzumaki",
            "Itachi",
            "Sasuke",
            "Sakura",
            "Kakashi Hatake",
            "All Might"
        ],
        "answer": "Kakashi Hatake"
    },
    {
        "question": "What army does Violet Evergarden serve?",
        "answers": [
            "Scout Regiment",
            "Legadonia Army",
            "The Empire",
            "Leidenschaftlich Army"
        ],
        "answer": "Leidenschaftlich Army"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sang \u2018Gurenge\u2019 from Demon Slayer?",
        "answers": [
            "Asaka",
            "MindaRyn",
            "Aimer",
            "LiSA"
        ],
        "answer": "LiSA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the names of Goku\u2019s sons?",
        "answers": [
            "Chi Chi and Gohan",
            "Pan and Goten",
            "Gohan and Trunks",
            "Trunks and Goten",
            "Gohan and Goten"
        ],
        "answer": "Gohan and Goten"
    },
    {
        "question": "What anime won Anime of the Year in Crunchyroll Anime Awards 2021?",
        "answers": [
            "Demon Slayer",
            "Attack on Titan",
            "Mushoku-tensei",
            "Jujutsu Kaisen"
        ],
        "answer": "Jujutsu Kaisen"
    },
    {
        "question": "What anime won Anime of the Year in Crunchyroll Anime Awards 2022?",
        "answers": [
            "Jujutsu Kaisen",
            "Komi-san",
            "Ousama Ranking",
            "Odd Taxi",
            "Sonny Boy",
            "Attack on Titan"
        ],
        "answer": "Attack on Titan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Studio Ghibli released the critically acclaimed film \u2018Your Name\u2019 \u2013 True or False?",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What genre is known to replicate real-life?",
        "answers": [
            "Isekai",
            "Romance",
            "Comedy",
            "Action",
            "Drama",
            "Slice of Life"
        ],
        "answer": "Slice of Life"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the biggest anime production company?",
        "answers": [
            "Funimation",
            "Crunchyroll",
            "Hulu",
            "Netflix",
            "Toei Animation"
        ],
        "answer": "Toei Animation"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do Dragon Ball fighters manipulate to blast energy?",
        "answers": [
            "Spirit",
            "Friendship",
            "Chakra",
            "Power Level",
            "Ki"
        ],
        "answer": "Ki"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many generations of Pok\u00e9mon are in the video game series?",
        "answers": [
            "7",
            "6",
            "5",
            "9",
            "8"
        ],
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vegeta and Goku are blood brothers \u2013 True or False?",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What art style features a small body and large head?",
        "answers": [
            "Ecchi",
            "Manhwa",
            "Hentai",
            "Chibi"
        ],
        "answer": "Chibi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What anime won Best Animation at the 2019 Crunchyroll Anime Awards?",
        "answers": [
            "Zombieland Saga",
            "Megalobox",
            "Devilman Crybaby",
            "Hinamatsuri",
            "Violet Evergarden"
        ],
        "answer": "Violet Evergarden"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Japanese voice of Light Yagami and Osamu Dazai in their respective animes?",
        "answers": [
            "Yuuki Kaji",
            "Hiroshi Kamiya",
            "Takehito Koyasu",
            "Mamoru Miyano"
        ],
        "answer": "Mamoru Miyano"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the sensei in Assassination Classroom?",
        "answers": [
            "Souma",
            "Nagisa",
            "Karma",
            "Octo-daddy",
            "Koro-sensei"
        ],
        "answer": "Koro-sensei"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fate/Stay Night was originally made as a visual novel before it was an anime series \u2013 True or False?",
        "answers": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "A common term used among anime watchers is \"The Big Three\". Which one of these animes is undisputedly one of these three giants?",
        "answers": [
            "Pokemon",
            "Fairy Tail",
            "Death Note",
            "One Piece"
        ],
        "answer": "One Piece"
    },
    {
        "question": "Here we have this charming little title where we get to see the human body in its daily operations. We follow a rookie Red Blood Cell, who has trouble getting her directions right, and a White Blood Cell killing bacteria and making good relations with the former. What is this title?",
        "answers": [
            "K-On!!",
            "Bacteria at Work",
            "Cell Lab",
            "Cells at Work!"
        ],
        "answer": "Cells at Work!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bounties. Bell peppers. Bang.",
        "answers": [
            "Outlaw Star",
            "Trigun",
            "Ghost in the Shell: Stand Alone Complex",
            "Cowboy Bebop"
        ],
        "answer": "Cowboy Bebop"
    },
    {
        "question": "I have a diary. I'm a criminal and a lover of explosives. I fell in love but my lover was killed. I have purple hair and an eyepatch. I was supposed to become a God but I refused. Who am I?",
        "answers": [
            "Yuno Gasai",
            "Yukiteru Amano",
            "Aru Akise",
            "Reisuke Houjou",
            "Minene Uryuu"
        ],
        "answer": "Minene Uryuu"
    },
    {
        "question": "I've been killed twice, yet I'm still here. I have to go out and follow orders from a toddler, and some stupid old hag is my mentor, who has also been killed once. I fight based on my emotions and I hate to lose.",
        "answers": [
            "Kyo",
            "Tamahome",
            "Kenshin",
            "Yusuke"
        ],
        "answer": "Yusuke"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \"Cowboy Bebop\", which of the following probably dies at the end of the show?",
        "answers": [
            "Faye,Isaiah",
            "Ed",
            "Spike"
        ],
        "answer": "Spike"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which experienced magical girl acts as a mentor figure to Madoka, only to be killed in front of her two episodes later by a Witch?",
        "answers": [
            "Nagisa Momoe",
            "Kyouko Sakura",
            "Sayaka Miki",
            "Mami Tomoe"
        ],
        "answer": "Mami Tomoe"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Isekai\" is a genre that refers to accidental travel, usually to another world in which the character starts a new life. Out of these comedic animes which one does not have Isekai as a genre?",
        "answers": [
            "Konosuba",
            "Isekai Cheat Magician",
            "Arifureta: From Commonplace to World's Strongest",
            "Kill La Kill"
        ],
        "answer": "Kill La Kill"
    },
    {
        "question": "One of the most popular titles in the anime world, this series follows an orange wearing ninja with a headstrong attitude and serious prankster vibe. Well, it's obvious it's called \"Naruto\", so I'll ask something else about the series. In what year did the original \"Naruto\" anime first air?",
        "answers": [
            "2001",
            "2003",
            "2004",
            "2002"
        ],
        "answer": "2002"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 'Senki Zesshou Symphogear G', the main trio of Hibiki, Tsubasa and Chris have to fight three enemy Symphogear users belonging to a mysterious organisation known as Fin\u00e9. Which Fin\u00e9 member is a European idol, wielded the Black Gungnir, and fought Tsubasa at a joint concert?",
        "answers": [
            "Shirabe Tsukuyomi",
            "Maria Cadenzavna Eve",
            "Kirika Akatsuki",
            "Serena Cadenzavna Eve"
        ],
        "answer": "Maria Cadenzavna Eve"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many siblings does Shinji have (Evangelion)?",
        "answers": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "None"
        ],
        "answer": "None"
    },
    {
        "question": "This next title is quite a romance, one of whacky plots and dysfunctional dynamics between a \"Palm Top Tiger\", and a mistaken delinquent. From that description, can you guess the title?",
        "answers": [
            "Rent a Girlfriend",
            "Love is War",
            "Oregairu",
            "Toradora!"
        ],
        "answer": "Toradora!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who lives in a house like this? Who lives in a house like this? A ginger magus, Shirou, lives in Number 12 He doesn't get on with his future self His Servant is King Arthur, but this version's a girl And Cu Chulainn's the unluckiest man in the world Oh, if you find the time, please come and stay a while In my anime neighbourhood",
        "answers": [
            "Violet Evergarden",
            "Dragon Maid",
            "Clannad",
            "Fate/stay night [Unlimited Blade Works]"
        ],
        "answer": "Fate/stay night [Unlimited Blade Works]"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 'Naruto Shippuuden', Naruto Uzumaki and co are up against the Akatsuki organisation, who wish to capture the nine Tailed Beasts. Konan, who uses paper as a weapon, is the only female member. Which Hidden Village does she come from?",
        "answers": [
            "Kirigakure",
            "Konohagakure",
            "Iwagakure",
            "Amegakure"
        ],
        "answer": "Amegakure"
    },
    {
        "question": "My mother died in a car accident and now I am staying with a family who possesses a horrible curse, but I have been sworn to secrecy. I have made very good friends within the family and feel as if I am one of them. I also... OH NO!! Have I left the bath running?!",
        "answers": [
            "Akito Sohma",
            "Yuki Sohma",
            "Kyo Soma",
            "Hatsuharu Sohma",
            "Shigure Sohma",
            "Tohru"
        ],
        "answer": "Tohru"
    },
    {
        "question": "In \"Yu Yu Hakusho\", what level computer does Mitari have to fight in Game Master's territory?",
        "answers": [
            "level 5",
            "level 10",
            "level 3",
            "level 12",
            "level 7"
        ],
        "answer": "level 7"
    },
    {
        "question": "This question is from \"Inu-Yasha\". I am a demon that was one of the very first enemies Inu-Yasha fought. I absolutely love Inu-Yasha's hair and I must have it, for I am a demon of hair. Who am I?",
        "answers": [
            "Yuri",
            "Yuro",
            "Yuki",
            "Yuuki",
            "Yura"
        ],
        "answer": "Yura"
    },
    {
        "question": "One of the Japanese closing themes to \"DragonBall Z\" is what?",
        "answers": [
            "Love Panic",
            "Ranma 1/2",
            "Groovy",
            "Yakusoko Wa Iranai",
            "We Were Angels",
            "Bokutechi Wa Tenshi Datta"
        ],
        "answer": "Bokutechi Wa Tenshi Datta"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the sins in Full Metal Alchemist: Brotherhood",
        "answers": [
            "Escanor Merlin Gowther King Ban Diane Meliodas",
            "Pride, Lust, Greed, Gluttony, Wrath, Sloth, Envy"
        ],
        "answer": "Pride, Lust, Greed, Gluttony, Wrath, Sloth, Envy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sin took over Ling Yao's Body?",
        "answers": [
            "Greed",
            "Envy",
            "Sloth",
            "Wrath"
        ],
        "answer": "Greed"
    },
    {
        "question": "At what age did Ed become a State Alchemist?",
        "answers": [
            "14",
            "8",
            "10",
            "12"
        ],
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these foods is Al most looking forward to eating once he gets his body back?",
        "answers": [
            "Pinako's Stew",
            "Winry's Pumpkin Pie",
            "Gracia's Apple pie",
            "Winry's Apple Pie"
        ],
        "answer": "Winry's Apple Pie"
    },
    {
        "question": "What date is carved into Ed's pocket watch as a reminder?",
        "answers": [
            "10 Oct 10",
            "3 Oct 3",
            "3 Nov 10",
            "3 Oct 11"
        ],
        "answer": "3 Oct 11"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal was never shown as part of a human chimera (FMA: B)?",
        "answers": [
            "Cow",
            "Gorilla",
            "Snake",
            "Cat"
        ],
        "answer": "Cat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the youngest Homunculus (FMA: B)?",
        "answers": [
            "Envy",
            "Sloth",
            "Greed",
            "Gluttony",
            "Lust",
            "Wrath"
        ],
        "answer": "Wrath"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the dog that stays at Winry's house in Resembool?",
        "answers": [
            "Sarah",
            "Hayate",
            "Yuriy",
            "Den"
        ],
        "answer": "Den"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the first Greed's hideout?",
        "answers": [
            "Devil's Rest",
            "Demon's Rest",
            "Demon's Rest",
            "Devil's Nest"
        ],
        "answer": "Devil's Nest"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two chimeras help Ed after he falls down a mine shaft in Baschool?",
        "answers": [
            "Darius and Zampano",
            "Zampano and Jerso",
            "Jerso and Heinkel",
            "Darius and Heinkel"
        ],
        "answer": "Darius and Heinkel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Barry the Chopper also known as (FMA: B)?",
        "answers": [
            "Number 33",
            "Number 58",
            "Number 48",
            "Number 66"
        ],
        "answer": "Number 66"
    },
    {
        "question": "What fake name does Lust use when talking to Jean Havoc (FMA: B)?",
        "answers": [
            "Laura",
            "Rebecca",
            "Asami",
            "Solaris"
        ],
        "answer": "Solaris"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the youngest member of the Armstrong family?",
        "answers": [
            "Philip",
            "Olivier",
            "Alex",
            "Catherine"
        ],
        "answer": "Catherine"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three countries exist right on the border of Amestris (FMA: B)?",
        "answers": [
            "Drachma Xing Ishval",
            "Drachma Creta Ishval",
            "Drachma Xing Aerugo",
            "Drachma Creta Ishval"
        ],
        "answer": "Drachma Creta Ishval"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the first song Ho-Kago Tea Time wrote and performed?",
        "answers": [
            "Fude Fude Pen",
            "U&I",
            "Tenshi ni Furetayo",
            "Fuwa Fuwa Time"
        ],
        "answer": "Fuwa Fuwa Time"
    },
    {
        "question": "What instrument does Ritsu play(K-on!!)",
        "answers": [
            "Keyboard",
            "Guitar",
            "Bass",
            "Drums"
        ],
        "answer": "Drums"
    },
    {
        "question": "Yui Hirasawa wrote the song \"U&I\" for which character(K-on!!)?",
        "answers": [
            "Mio Akiyama",
            "Sawako-sensei",
            "Azusa Nakano",
            "Ui Hirasawa"
        ],
        "answer": "Ui Hirasawa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which member of Ho-kago Tea Time is prone to getting sunburnt (K-on!!)?",
        "answers": [
            "Mio Akiyama",
            "Tsumugi Kotobuki",
            "Yui Hirasawa",
            "Ritsu Tanaka",
            "Azusa Nakano"
        ],
        "answer": "Azusa Nakano"
    },
    {
        "question": "What instrument does Tsumugi Kotobuki play(K-on!!)?",
        "answers": [
            "Guitar",
            "Bass",
            "Drums",
            "Keyboard"
        ],
        "answer": "Keyboard"
    },
    {
        "question": "What instrument does Mio Akiyama play (K-on!!)?",
        "answers": [
            "Keyboard",
            "Guitar",
            "Drums",
            "Bass"
        ],
        "answer": "Bass"
    },
    {
        "question": "What instrument does Yui Hirasawa play (K-on!!)?",
        "answers": [
            "Keyboard",
            "Bass",
            "Drums",
            "Guitar"
        ],
        "answer": "Guitar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What instrument does Azusa Nakano play (K-on!!)?",
        "answers": [
            "Bass",
            "Keyboard",
            "Drums",
            "Guitar"
        ],
        "answer": "Guitar"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Ho-kago Tea Time band went on a trip together before graduation what country did they go to (K-on!!)?",
        "answers": [
            "Egypt",
            "Kyoto",
            "Tokyo",
            "Hiroshima",
            "London"
        ],
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many seconds does Gojo ask to have with Itadori's \"Sukuna\" form?",
        "answers": [
            "15",
            "20",
            "6",
            "7",
            "10"
        ],
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of weapon does Nobara use to exorcise curses?",
        "answers": [
            "Sword",
            "Spear",
            "Bow",
            "Hammer"
        ],
        "answer": "Hammer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What task taught Itadori to control his emotions while using cursed energy to keep a doll asleep (JJK)?",
        "answers": [
            "Training Martial Arts",
            "Listening to Music",
            "Watching Gojou Fight",
            "Watching Movies"
        ],
        "answer": "Watching Movies"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Gojo fighting when he teaches Itadori about domain expansion?",
        "answers": [
            "Mahito",
            "Suguru Geto",
            "Hanami",
            "Jogo"
        ],
        "answer": "Jogo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did Itadori and Nanami investigate the massacre by Mahito?",
        "answers": [
            "A Mall",
            "A Grocery Store",
            "A friend's House",
            "A Movie Theatre"
        ],
        "answer": "A Movie Theatre"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the class pet for the Light Music Club (K-on!!)?",
        "answers": [
            "Dog",
            "Cat",
            "Bird",
            "Turtle"
        ],
        "answer": "Turtle"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Demon Slayer, which hashira was the one that stabbed Nezuko Kamado?",
        "answers": [
            "Giyuu Tomioka",
            "Shinobu Kocho",
            "Gyomei Himejima",
            "Kyujuro Rengoku",
            "Mitsuri Kanroji",
            "Sanemi Shinazugawa"
        ],
        "answer": "Sanemi Shinazugawa"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Demon Slayer, what breathing form do other breathing forms derive from?",
        "answers": [
            "Moon Breathing",
            "Fire Breathing",
            "Wind Breathing",
            "Water Breathing",
            "Sun Breathing"
        ],
        "answer": "Sun Breathing"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Demon Slayer, what is Tanjiro Kamado's greatest sense?",
        "answers": [
            "Sight",
            "Taste",
            "Hearing",
            "Awareness",
            "Smell"
        ],
        "answer": "Smell"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Demon Slayer, what is Inosuke's greatest sense?",
        "answers": [
            "Smell",
            "Sight",
            "Taste",
            "Hearing",
            "Awareness"
        ],
        "answer": "Awareness"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Demon Slayer, what is Zenitsu Agatsuma's greatest sense?",
        "answers": [
            "Awareness",
            "Smell",
            "Taste",
            "Sight",
            "Hearing"
        ],
        "answer": "Hearing"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first Hashira that Tanjiro met in the mountains?",
        "answers": [
            "Tengen Uzui",
            "Shinobu Kocho",
            "Sankonji Urokodaki",
            "Kyojuro Rengoku",
            "Giyuu Tomioka"
        ],
        "answer": "Giyuu Tomioka"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a demon's greatest weakness (Demon Slayer)?",
        "answers": [
            "Wisteria",
            "Sun Breathing",
            "Water Breathing",
            "Nichirin Blades",
            "Saitama",
            "Sunlight"
        ],
        "answer": "Sunlight"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many days did Tanjiro have to survive for the Final Selection?",
        "answers": [
            "14 days",
            "5 days",
            "4",
            "days",
            "10 days",
            "7 days"
        ],
        "answer": "7 days"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Demon Slayer always gets Tanjiro's name wrong?",
        "answers": [
            "Zenitsu Agatsuma",
            "Genya Shinazugawa",
            "Kanao Kocho",
            "Giyuu Tomioka",
            "Inosuke Hashibira"
        ],
        "answer": "Inosuke Hashibira"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who are the two demons on the run from Kibutsuji?",
        "answers": [
            "Tamayo and Enmu",
            "Tamayo and Yushiro",
            "Nezuko and Tanjiro",
            "Rui and Enmu"
        ],
        "answer": "Tamayo and Yushiro"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the drum demon who was removed from the Kizuki?",
        "answers": [
            "Enmu",
            "Rui",
            "Kyosuke",
            "Akaza",
            "Tamayo",
            "Kyogai"
        ],
        "answer": "Kyogai"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Tanjiro sell before he became a Demon Slayer?",
        "answers": [
            "Wood",
            "Lumber",
            "Iron Ore",
            "Food",
            "Hay",
            "Charcoal"
        ],
        "answer": "Charcoal"
    },
    {
        "question": "After feeling dissatisfied with the lower moons, Kibutsuji decides to kill how many of his five remaining demons (Demon Slayer)?",
        "answers": [
            "3",
            "5",
            "2",
            "6",
            "4"
        ],
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Muzan Kibutsuji has a human family (Demon Slayer).",
        "answers": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In No Game No Life, how old is Shiro?",
        "answers": [
            "7",
            "13",
            "8",
            "14",
            "16",
            "11"
        ],
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "In No Game No Life, what is Sora's occupation?",
        "answers": [
            "Student",
            "Office Worker",
            "Writer",
            "Professional Gamer",
            "NEET"
        ],
        "answer": "NEET"
    },
    {
        "question": "In No Game No Life, what is the name of the world Sora and Shiro are transported to?",
        "answers": [
            "Earth",
            "Asteria",
            "Amestria",
            "Asterisk",
            "Disboard"
        ],
        "answer": "Disboard"
    },
    {
        "question": "In No Game No Life, what is the name of the god of play?",
        "answers": [
            "Vishnu",
            "Aragabaki",
            "Berith",
            "Mars",
            "Tet"
        ],
        "answer": "Tet"
    },
    {
        "question": "In No Game No Life, what game did Shiro beat Tet in to make it to Disboard?",
        "answers": [
            "Shogi",
            "Checkers",
            "First Person Shooter",
            "Human Chess",
            "Chess"
        ],
        "answer": "Chess"
    },
    {
        "question": "In No Game No Life, which of the 16 Exceed have the greatest affinity for magic?",
        "answers": [
            "Ex Machina",
            "Werebeast",
            "Imanity",
            "Lunamana",
            "Phantasma",
            "Flugel",
            "Old Deus"
        ],
        "answer": "Old Deus"
    },
    {
        "question": "In No Game No Life, Which of the Exceed do Sora and Shiro rule over?",
        "answers": [
            "Ex Machina",
            "Werebeast",
            "Lunamana",
            "Phantasma",
            "Flugel",
            "Imanity"
        ],
        "answer": "Imanity"
    },
    {
        "question": "In No Game No Life, at the end of season 1, how many Race Pieces does Sora and Shiro have?",
        "answers": [
            "1",
            "3",
            "4",
            "2"
        ],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "In No Game No Life, which is the most knowledgeable of the Exceed?",
        "answers": [
            "Seiren",
            "Imanity",
            "Old Deus",
            "Ex-Machina",
            "Werebeast",
            "Lunamana",
            "Phantasma",
            "Flugel"
        ],
        "answer": "Flugel"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Akame ga Kill, how did Sieu and Eiasu die in the first episode?",
        "answers": [
            "They got killed by a night raid",
            "They got killed by tatsumi",
            "They did not die",
            "Tatsumi killed them",
            "They were tortured to death"
        ],
        "answer": "They were tortured to death"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Akame ga Kill, who does esdeath love the most?",
        "answers": [
            "Akame",
            "Lubbock",
            "Bulat",
            "Susanoo",
            "Tatsumi"
        ],
        "answer": "Tatsumi"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Akame ga Kill, where does Tatsumi get his Teigu from?",
        "answers": [
            "Lubbock",
            "Akame",
            "Mine",
            "Chelsea",
            "Leone",
            "Bulat"
        ],
        "answer": "Bulat"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Akame ga Kill, what is Murasame's ability?",
        "answers": [
            "Always stays sharp",
            "Cut through time",
            "Freezes time",
            "Kill anything it cuts"
        ],
        "answer": "Kill anything it cuts"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Assassination Classroom, who was the first student to harm Koro-sensei?",
        "answers": [
            "Nagisa",
            "Kaede",
            "Tadaomi",
            "Irina",
            "Itona",
            "Karma"
        ],
        "answer": "Karma"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Assassination Classroom, Koro-sensei was once an assassin known as \"The Reaper\"",
        "answers": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the first episode of Assassination Classroom, what did the students first attempt to do to kill Koro-sensei?",
        "answers": [
            "Attempted to poison him",
            "Attempted to all ambush him with Koro-sensei killing knives",
            "BB pellet grenades",
            "Shoot rifles at him"
        ],
        "answer": "Shoot rifles at him"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Assassination classroom, who is Reaper 2.0?",
        "answers": [
            "A Reaper Copycat",
            "The students PE Teacher",
            "Koro-sensei's Stalker",
            "Koro-sensei's old apprentice"
        ],
        "answer": "Koro-sensei's old apprentice"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Assassination Classroom, how fast can Koro-sensei travel up to?",
        "answers": [
            "Mach 17",
            "Mach 10",
            "Mach 16",
            "Mach 20"
        ],
        "answer": "Mach 20"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Assassination Classroom, which students always gets mistaken for a female?",
        "answers": [
            "Karma",
            "Kaede",
            "Gakushuu",
            "Itona",
            "Ritsu",
            "Nagisa"
        ],
        "answer": "Nagisa"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Assassination Classroom, which student also has Koro-sensei's tentacle abilities and believed Koro-sensei killed her sister.",
        "answers": [
            "Nagisa Shiota",
            "Karma Akabane",
            "Itona Horibe",
            "Ritsu",
            "Kaede Kayano"
        ],
        "answer": "Kaede Kayano"
    },
    {
        "question": "In No Game No Life, how old is Sora?",
        "answers": [
            "14",
            "15",
            "16",
            "17",
            "18"
        ],
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won best girl in Crunchyroll 2022 Anime Awards?",
        "answers": [
            "Komi Shoko",
            "Tohru Honda",
            "Vladilena Milize",
            "Ai Ohto",
            "Sarasa Watanabe",
            "Nobara Kugisaki"
        ],
        "answer": "Nabara Kugisaki"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won best boy in Crunchyroll 2022 Anime Awards?",
        "answers": [
            "Senku Ishigami",
            "Odokawa",
            "Izumi Miyamura",
            "Ken 'Draken' Ryuguji",
            "Manijiro 'Mikey' Sano",
            "Bojji"
        ],
        "answer": "Bojji"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won best antagnoist in Crunchyroll 2022 Anime Awards?",
        "answers": [
            "Yano",
            "Echidna",
            "Tomura Shigaraki",
            "Tetta Kisaki",
            "Eren Jaeger"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren Jaeger"
    },
    {
        "question": "In One Punch Man, what was Saitama's occupation before becoming a profession hero?",
        "answers": [
            "University Student",
            "Pizza Delivery Man",
            "Grocery Store Clerk",
            "Business Man"
        ],
        "answer": "Business Man"
    },
    {
        "question": "In One Punch Man, what is Saitama's workout routine?",
        "answers": [
            "100 situps | 100 pushups | 100 squats | 100 km run",
            "100 crunches | 100 pushups | 100 squats | 100 km run",
            "1000 situps | 1000 pushups | 1000 squats | 100km run",
            "100 situps | 100 pushups | 100 squats | 10km run"
        ],
        "answer": "100 situps | 100 pushups | 100 squats | 10km run"
    },
    {
        "question": "In One Punch Man, Boros is the leader of what group?",
        "answers": [
            "ALien Conquerers",
            "Black Matter Alliance",
            "Monster Association",
            "Dark Matter Thieves"
        ],
        "answer": "Dark Matter Thieves"
    },
    {
        "question": "What game did Saitama catch King playing (One Punch Man)?",
        "answers": [
            "Purrfect Date",
            "Super Fight",
            "Cute Honey",
            "Doki Doki Sisters"
        ],
        "answer": "Doki Doki Sisters"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Hero rank is Fubuki (Hellish Blizzard) in One Punch Man?",
        "answers": [
            "A",
            "B",
            "C",
            "D",
            "S",
            "F",
            "B"
        ],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "In his fight with Boros, Saitama gets hit so hard, he flies to ___ (One Punch Man)?",
        "answers": [
            "Mars",
            "The US",
            "The Sun",
            "Across the Globe",
            "The Moon"
        ],
        "answer": "The Moon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these characters is not an S class hero in One Punch Man?",
        "answers": [
            "Watchdog Man",
            "Flashy Flash",
            "Tanktop Master",
            "Amai Mask"
        ],
        "answer": "Amai Mask"
    },
    {
        "question": "In One Punch Man, who killed Zombieman?",
        "answers": [
            "Sitch",
            "Atomic Samurai",
            "Child Emperor",
            "Sonic",
            "Bang",
            "Tatsumaki"
        ],
        "answer": "Tatsumaki"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these is NOT a member of the Monster Association (One Punch Man)?",
        "answers": [
            "Elder Centipede",
            "Marshall Gorilla",
            "Awakend Cockroach",
            "Garou"
        ],
        "answer": "Garou"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who turned Genos into a cyborg?",
        "answers": [
            "Dr. Wiley",
            "Dr. Genus",
            "Dr. Fukegao",
            "Dr. Kuseno"
        ],
        "answer": "Dr. Kuseno"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Hunter x Hunter, who was the \"Rookie Crusher\" of the Hunter Exam?",
        "answers": [
            "Killua Zoldyck",
            "Gittarackur",
            "Hisoka Morow",
            "Hanzo",
            "Tonpa"
        ],
        "answer": "Tonpa"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Greed Island Arc, what did Killua say his yo-yos were made out of?",
        "answers": [
            "Silver",
            "Steel",
            "Katchin",
            "Superalloy"
        ],
        "answer": "Superalloy"
    },
    {
        "question": "At the end of the Greed Island Arc, Bisky obtained the Blue Planet, but what nickname did she give it?",
        "answers": [
            "Blue-chan",
            "Blue Stone",
            "Shiny Stone",
            "Planet-chan"
        ],
        "answer": "Planet-chan"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many openings did Hunter x Hunter (2011) have?",
        "answers": [
            "2",
            "3",
            "5",
            "1"
        ],
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Throughout Hunter x Hunter, what was Gon's Nen type?",
        "answers": [
            "Conjuration",
            "Manipulation",
            "Emission",
            "Transmutation",
            "Specialization",
            "Enhancement"
        ],
        "answer": "Enhancement"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is/are the property/properties of Hisoka's Bungee gum?",
        "answers": [
            "Bungee and Gum",
            "Rubber",
            "Gum",
            "Rubber and Gum"
        ],
        "answer": "Rubber and Gum"
    },
    {
        "question": "When three of Alluka's wishes are granted, who does Alluka transform into.",
        "answers": [
            "Mitsuba",
            "Tsubone",
            "Amane",
            "Nanika"
        ],
        "answer": "Nanika"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Alluka's biological gender (Hunter x Hunter)?",
        "answers": [
            "Male",
            "Female"
        ],
        "answer": "Male"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Zoldyck estate, how much does the 7th testing gate weigh?",
        "answers": [
            "128 tons",
            "76 tons",
            "180 tons",
            "256 tons"
        ],
        "answer": "256 tons"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Royal Guard made Gon transform?",
        "answers": [
            "Meruem",
            "Shaiapouf",
            "Menthuthuyoupi",
            "Neferpitou"
        ],
        "answer": "Neferpitou"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the advanced application of Ten and Ren?",
        "answers": [
            "Ryu",
            "Ken",
            "Ko",
            "En"
        ],
        "answer": "En"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the town where Kazuma and Aqua first arrive (Konosuba)?",
        "answers": [
            "Amestris",
            "Asterisk",
            "Amestrian",
            "Axel"
        ],
        "answer": "Axel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Kazuma's highest stats when he initially got placed in the world (Konosuba)?",
        "answers": [
            "Intelligence",
            "Dexterity",
            "Magic",
            "Strength",
            "Luck"
        ],
        "answer": "Luck"
    },
    {
        "question": "What name did Megumin gave to Kazuma's sword?",
        "answers": [
            "Chop Chopper",
            "Chop Sword",
            "Chun Chun Mari",
            "Elucidator",
            "Maru",
            "Chun Chun Maru"
        ],
        "answer": "Chun Chun Maru"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose sword did Kazuma steal and sell (KonoSuba)?",
        "answers": [
            "Yunyun",
            "Vanir",
            "Eris",
            "Wiz",
            "Darkness",
            "Mitsurugi Kyouya"
        ],
        "answer": "Mitsurugi Kyouya"
    }
]